articlesark.com 2012-09-27

# Privacy Policy

Online Free Articles Directory

### Search More Articles

Your privacy is very important to us and it is our responsibility to protect the data you provide to us in normal circumstances. This Privacy Policy provides you the explanation on how Articles Ark collects, uses, and discloses the personal information provided by you as a result of the use of Articles Ark’s Web Site. We hope that our comprehensive privacy policy below will help you to better understand what data we collect and how we use it.

### Information Collection and Use

  * Articles Ark collects personal information such as your name, email address, etc. when you register for author account.
  * We use this information in order to contact you and provide you further information about our company and services.
  * We may use the personal information you provided to give the services you requested and for our own research and analysis to improve on the services and products that we deliver, as well as develop new services and products.
  * We may share this information with our authorized partners and/or with third parties who act for or on behalf of us, but we do not otherwise provide or sell any information gathered on this Site to outside vendors.

### Information Sharing and Disclosure

  * Your contact information is never released or sold to any vendor, partner or outside agency. Articles Ark, however, reserves the right to contact Articles Ark members via email as deemed necessary.
  * The Articles Ark web site has reasonable security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control.
  * You can decline to submit personal information for any of our services, in which case Articles Ark may not be able to provide services to you.

### Hyperlinks

  * This site contains links to other 3rd party sites and these sites are not covered under our privacy policy.
  * We do not assure any responsibility, liability for, or control over other web sites links.
  * When you leave the Articles Ark Site via one of the links then we recommend you to read the privacy policy, if any, provided by the site that you have visited.

### Legal Disclaimer

Though we make efforts to preserve your privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary in order to conform to the decree of the law or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.

### Use of Cookies

Articles Ark store loggined user information in cookies for keeping the session alive

Articles Ark uses third party adserver Google.

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.
  * Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy.](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)
  * We partner with ValueClick Media to serve ads and/or collect certain information when you visit our website. ValueClick Media may use cookies or web beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visit to this website in order to help show advertisements on other websites likely to be more interesting to you. To learn more about this “behavioral advertising” practice or to opt-out of this use of your anonymous information, you can visit [ValueClick Media Website](https://admin.valueclickmedia.com/optout/index.html)

### Change in Privacy Policy

Articles Ark may revise the privacy policy from time to time. Readers are encouraged to check the policy from time to time; however, if significant changes are made in the way your personal information is used, we will post a prominent announcement on our site notifying you of the change.
